Deti Nadya Rahma

Palembang 30153 | +6282176075369 detinadya@gmail.com

PERSONAL SUMMARY

A confident and reliable IT Support with extensive practical experience in working with computers and resolving any support issues raised to the service desk. I have experience working on the front line helping clients and colleagues resolve complex technical IT issues. Possesses a proven ability to administer and control computer-based information systems, has an eye for detail, and can multitask under pressure. An excellent communicator and has the flexibility of being a team member and on my own.

EXPERIENCE

IT Support Officer

Juni 2022 - Now

Ernaldi Bahar Psychiatric Hospital of South Sumatera Province, Palembang

- Operated and conducted Hospital Information System (HIS).
- Analyze and develop updated HIS with the latest regulation from the Health Ministry of Indonesia.
- Ensure the strong quality of the system in accordance with the needs of the users.
- Testing the updated application (manual testing).
- IT helpdesk and support users' requirements.

IT Recruiter (Freelance)

Feb 2022 - Mei 2022

Nexroar Sdn. Bhd, Kuala Lumpur

- Arranged 10+ interviews daily.
- Managed the full recruiting process from sourcing, interviewing, and coordinating hiring process.
- Managed recruiting databases and other HR assets in structured and timely manners.
- Reporting to Sr. IT recruiter and HRD.
- Scouting potential candidates from Linkedin, Monster, other social media.
- Approached the candidate and explaining the job descriptions.

IT Support and Administrator

Oct 2019 - Aug 2021

Siti Fatimah General Hospital of South Sumatera Province, Palembang

- Trained as a Hospital Information System admin and periodically analyzed the development.
- Provide technical support to 10+ Departments in the company.
- Provide day-to-day support to ensure the smooth running of the computer, network devices, printers, and end users' requirements.
- Supporting user and network administrator over the telephone and by desktop remote.
- Assisting with the training of staff and compiling procedural documentation.
- Handling administration tasks in IT Department and making annual report documentation.
- Setting a virtual meeting via Zoom, Google Meet, Cisco Webex, and Ms. Teams.
- Responsible as an IT recruiter for an internship in the hospital.

IT Support Feb 2018 - Jul 2019

Airan Raya Hospital of South Lampung, Lampung Selatan

- Manage IT infrastructure, system monitoring, and reports.
- Monitoring and maintenance of CCTV in the building.
- Implement and monitor IT security and antivirus.
- Other duties include performing first-level troubleshooting.
- Assistance with the training of new staff about Hospital Information System.
- Deploying new hardware, server backups, and evaluating new software.
- Configuring and managing backup and restore procedures.

EDUCATION

Bachelor's Degree Informatics Engineering (IT)

Aug 2010 - Jul 2015

Sriwijaya University, Palembang

SKILLS

Intermediate in: Creative and Innovative, Communication, Problem Solving, Time

Management, Team Leader, Troubleshoot, Web Design, UI/UX Design

Basic in: Data Science, Software Testing, Quality Assurance

LICENSES & CERTIFICATIONS

Sanbercode - 17031/65/BDG/P-SNBR/CODE/2021

Quality Assurance Sanbercode - 33404/288/SNBR/BOOTCAMP/VIII/2022	2022
Laravel Web Development Sanbercode - 19107/71/BDG/P-SNBR/CODE/2021	2021
Machine Learning -Data Science JakartaLabs - 001/JL-ML-W5/VII/2021	2021
III/IIX Design	2021

VOLUNTEER

Exchange ParticipantDec 2012 - Feb 2013

AIESEC UNSRI INDONESIA - AIESEC NCKU TAIWAN